- Everywhere we go
- People wanna know
- Who we are
- So we tell them
- We are Artillery
- Mighty fine Artillery
- Everywhere we go
- People wanna know
- Who we are
- First Platoon, Company B
- We're the best you'll ever see
- Company B, Artillery
Go left, go left, go left, right, left.
- Everywhere we go
- People wanna know
Keep up the pace.
Left. Go to the left.
- Everywhere we go
- People wanna know...
Ten-hut!
Stubble.
I'm looking at stubble, private.
- When did you shave?
- I shaved this morning, sir.
You are supposed to clean
the billets in the morning.
Company punishment.
More stubble.
- When did you shave, soldier?
- I shaved last night, sir.
Army regulations say
you will shave every morning.
Company punishment.
Tell me you're feeling
better today, private.
Yes, sir.
Sergeant.
Sir.
Well, troopers,
looks like you messed up again,
which means field exercises again.
Tonight, 1 800 hours.
Sound good to you?
Yes, sir.
- You can thank whoever left this.
- Sir.
Thomas and I
just cleaned the latrine, sir.
There was no cigarette butt in there.
Then maybe you're the ones
that they should thank.
At ease.
That lousy...
Bobby, Bobby, you okay?
Stomach cramps again, man.
If it was something you ate,
you'd be over it by now.
It's gotta be some kind of a bug.
Maybe so.
Maybe the next one to get it
will be Walters, you know?
Forget it, Bobby. You're not
going out in the field tonight.
You go on sick call.
And face Walters?
No, man. No way.
Crawling around in the dark
is a picnic compared to Walters.
Yeah.
Go! Out of there! Come on!
Hustle, hustle!
I got a grandmother
who moves faster than you!
Come on!
All right, gentlemen,
observe the wooded area
in front of you.
C Company made it
across that terrain and back
in two hours and 1 7 minutes.
That used to be the fort record.
I say ''used to be'' because you
are going to make it across and back
in two hours and ten minutes.
- Got it?
- Yes, sir!
Then move them out.
Left face, double-time march.
Bobby? Bobby, come on.
Move it, Thomas, move it.
What, your skirt get wet? Come on.
- Lay off him. He's got cramps again.
- I'm okay.
Bobby, you can't do this.
Go back. Forget about Walters.
Hey, hey! Where do you think
you're going, Thomas?
Where do you think you're going?
Thomas!
He's sick, sarge.
What are you doing here?
- Sir, I can't continue the exercise.
- Get back out there.
Sir, I'm sick. My insides are cramping
so bad I can hardly move.
I'm the one who's getting sick
of mama's boys like you.
Your soul may belong to God,
Thomas, but your butt belongs to me,
and if you don't move it on out there
on the double and rejoin that unit,
I am gonna teach you what pain is.
Is that what you want?
- No, sir.
- Then move out!
I'll never catch up now.
Follow that stream, about 200 yards,
cross it, head west,
and you'll cut them off.
Now, haul it!
Fall out.
All right, listen up.
Two hours
and 21 minutes.
Guess we'll just have to do this
more often.
You do wanna break that record,
don't you?
- Yes, sir.
- All right.
Smoke them if you got them.
Where's Thomas, sir?
I sent the pansy back out.
Back out where?
He's not with us, sir.
All right, everybody.
Back on your feet.
Fan out over the line of march
and locate Private Thomas.
Everybody up! Come on! Let's go!
Move!
You had no business sending him
back out there.
He was sick.
You arguing with me soldier?
- I'm just telling you, sir.
- Shut up.
And go find your little friend.
Thomas!
Bobby! Bobby!
Bobby!
- Thomas!
- Bobby!
Bobby!
Hey, he's over here! Get a medic!
Bobby.
Can I help you?
Hey, kid, this place
would be off-limits to you
even if we didn't have a dress code.
I'm talking to you.
You lost, soldier?
Bobby Thomas' appendix
ruptured tonight.
I just came from the hospital.
Bobby's dead and you killed him.
At ease, Hughes.
- You go to hell!
- That's enough, private.
- You're addressing an officer.
- He's not fit to be an officer.
He killed one of his own men.
Bobby Thomas died tonight
because you sent him back out there
- even though you knew he was sick.
- Get out.
You're easier to read
than Mother Goose.
Lieutenant.
Sit down.
- You're gonna pay.
- At ease, private. That's an order.
They're gonna investigate.
I'm gonna tell them what happened.
They're finally gonna nail you.
Private Hughes, you will consider
yourself confined to quarters.
- Do I make myself clear?
- Yes, sir.
My God, Ray.
As he said,
there will be an investigation.
Walters.
Ever consider that maybe
you push your luck?
- Hey, hey
- Red Beret
- Second Squad
- Lead the way
- Hey, hey
- Red Beret
- Second Squad
- Lead the way
- Hey, hey
- Red Beret
- Second Squad
- Lead the way
Soldier, you're in deep trouble.
I went off the base for the night.
I'm back now.
Lieutenant Walters
was murdered last night.
- Murdered?
- Stabbed to death
in the officer's club with this.
- I found it in your footlocker.
- Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
He was alive when I left last night.
You saw me.
Somebody else saw you there
20 minutes later,
after everybody
but the lieutenant had left.
- That's a lie.
- You save it for the court-martial.
Place him in custody.
Ben.
- Arthur.
- Ben, I have a problem.
Don't yell, Arthur.
I know I should've waited till tomorrow
and come to your office.
That's right, Arthur.
I don't talk business on Sunday.
This is an emergency.
- I don't care, Arthur.
- It's about Chris.
- I heard.
- You've gotta help him, Ben.
I have to be in Germany tomorrow
to close a deal
I've been working on for two years.
Now, I need your help.
I spoke to Chris a little while ago
and I told him that you'd be down
to talk to him right away.
It's not right for you to come driving
out here and stomping up on my porch
and telling me that you promised Chris
I'd be down there to see him
in a little while. You want some
of this chicken sandwich?
- Will you listen to me?
- You've always been that way, Arthur.
They have him on a murder charge.
As long as I can remember,
you've come stomping up on my porch
and telling me what I have to do.
Now, I'm working on other cases
right now.
Postpone them.
Anytime you want something
or you're in some kind of trouble,
you expect everybody
to drop everything.
The Army will appoint him a lawyer.
Chris has got an attitude problem.
I was hoping the Army
was going to knock that out of him.
I don't remember Chris
having an attitude problem.
I remember you always had
an attitude problem.
I don't think he's got a prayer
without someone like you.
- Arthur.
- Please.
The Army doesn't like civilians
messing in their stuff.
Look, Ben, why don't we
just cut through all this?
I know that your standard
rich-client fee is $1 00,000.
I am going to write a cheque
for 1 50,000.
Two hundred thousand?
Two hundred and fifty
thousand dollars.
I'll go down and see Chris.
Make out the cheque for $1 00,000.
How much it's going to cost you
when it's all over
depends on how mad I get at you.
Tell me about the night of the murder.
Well...
When they pronounced Bobby
Thomas dead--
He was a young man that
the lieutenant killed on manoeuvres.
--well, I was so angry
I went down to the officers' club
and I tried to get
into a fight with him.
Who else was there?
The lieutenant was there
with Colonel McRea,
Captain Campbell,
Major Hamilton,
and Lieutenant Lynch.
They were playing poker.
- See anybody else?
- No. Just the bartender.
- It was late.
- Then you left.
- Yeah.
- Where'd you go when you left?
Then I drove around
for a couple hours.
I finally wound up at Nancy's.
She's this girl I know in town.
I spent the rest of the night there.
So there's no way you can prove
where you were
at the time of the murder.
No.
This bayonet they found
in your footlocker,
- any idea who put it there?
- No.
The fella who says he saw you
come back to the club,
any idea why he'd lie?
No idea.
Not much to go on, is there?
Why'd you come down here?
Chris,
I take cases for three reasons.
Sometimes I'll take a case for money
and I don't think that's wrong.
It doesn't bother me.
That's the way I make my living.
Sometimes I take one because
clearly an injustice is being done.
Sometimes I'll take one
because it interests me.
But somewhere in my mind,
I must believe
the person I represent is innocent.
What about me?
I think an injustice is being done
and the case interests me.
That answer any of your questions?
Yeah.
Let's say we get together
and do this.
Yeah. Okay.
I better go or I'll be late
for my appointment
with the base commander.
- Sergeant.
- Mr. Matlock,
what do you think my chances are?
Oh, there's always
a fighting chance.
The truth has a way of coming out.
See if I can get you out of here.
Go left, go left, go left, right, left.
Go left, go left, go left, right...
Go left, go left...
Morning, sir.
Excuse me, son.
Yes, sir.
- I seem to be lost.
- How can I help you, sir?
I'm looking for
General Connors' office.
Headquarters is two blocks up
the road, second door on the right, sir.
- Thank you.
- Anytime sir.
Arthur Hughes and I
go back to OCS.
He left the Army
after about three years.
I decided to stay.
And you kept in touch all this time.
Mr. Matlock,
this is awkward for me.
I hope you understand my position.
Not exactly.
Well, an investigating officer
whom I've already appointed
will be conducting
an Article 32 investigation.
That's a hearing where testimony and
evidence are presented to the officer,
and then he, in turn,
presents his hearings to me.
Well, it's been up to me to determine
whether or not a court-martial
is warranted.
Well, I'm concerned about Chris.
How can I get him out
of the stockade?
Well, that's not so simple.
Would you ask Major Orlando
to step in here, please?
He's our staff judge advocate.
You'll have to discuss
Private Hughes' release with him.
- I'd be delighted.
- Don't be too sure.
Yeah.
Major Orlando, Benjamin Matlock.
Mr. Matlock
is Private Hughes' attorney.
He'd like him released
from the stockade.
That is not possible, sir.
I'm not asking that he be freed,
just released from the stockade
and placed under
some kind of house arrest.
The evidence against
Private Hughes is overwhelming.
You think he's guilty?
What I meant to say is that,
well, Private Hughes
has already gone AWOL once.
What's to prevent him
from doing it again?
With a base full of soldiers?
Surely somebody
can keep an eye on him.
Release Private Hughes from the
stockade and confine him to quarters.
Yes, sir.
Anything else?
I'd like to take a look at the scene of
the crime, if it's not too much trouble.
I'll have the provost marshal meet you
at the officer's club ASAP.
Fine. And then I'd like to go through
all of that overwhelming evidence.
Anytime.
- Morning, sir.
Morning.
Morning, what can I get for you?
How about a cup of coffee
and a little information?
What kind of information?
Well, this is my first day on the post.
- I didn't enlist. I'm a civilian.
- Makes two of us.
Everywhere I go, these young fellas
salute and call me sir.
I might get to like that if I knew why.
They get a lot of visitors around here,
VIP types.
The boys see somebody like you,
you know, white hair and everything,
think you're some kind of bigshot,
like a congressman or maybe a senator.
I figured it was my suit.
- Mr. Matlock?
- Yes.
Major Jeffrey Hamilton,
provost marshal.
If you'll follow me,
I'll show you the scene of the crime.
Yes, sir.
Excuse my ignorance, major,
but what's a provost marshal?
- Head MP.
- Oh, kind of like the chief of police.
I see.
I understand you were here
the night of the murder.
That's right. Playing poker.
What time did the game break up?
About 1 0:45 or so.
Well, why didn't Lieutenant Walters
leave with the rest of you?
He stayed behind
to run some totals.
He kept a book
on what everyone owed.
I'd like to see that.
- See what?
- The book.
Is it with the rest
of the evidence or what?
Actually, it was never found.
You mean the killer took it?
Well, why would Chris Hughes
be concerned with the accounts
of a poker game?
I have no idea.
Why don't you ask him?
How do you suppose he knew
Lieutenant Walters
was in here by himself?
Maybe he waited for him outside
and just got lucky.
Maybe.
But then we know
there were several people
who knew positively
that Lieutenant Walters
was in here alone, don't we?
One, two, three, four people.
Are you suggesting
that one of us killed him?
No, no, no.
You were obviously friends,
playing cards like that.
I'd like my investigator
to look around in here.
Our forensics people
have already gone over this room
with a fine-toothed comb.
We'll send you a copy of the report.
Now, if there's nothing--
It's customary for the defence
to have the opportunity
to examine the scene of the crime.
You just did.
I just did.
Where'd you go
after the poker game?
Back to my office,
till midnight,
catching up on some paperwork.
This Sergeant Owens who said he saw
Chris come back to the club that night,
where would I find him?
- He works in post supply.
-Where is that?
You go out the front door, turn left,
three blocks, left.
It'll be right in front of you.
- Sergeant Owens?
- Yes, sir.
My name's Ben Matlock.
I'm an attorney.
I'd like to ask some questions.
About what?
About what you saw the night
Lieutenant Walters was murdered.
Well, I'm sorry, sir,
but I got a lot of work to do.
Couldn't you work and talk
at the same time?
Sergeant?
Hey, Sergeant.
Wait a minute!
Oh, no. No way. Absolutely not.
Not in a million years.
Out of the question.
Tyler, let me put it this way:
You have to.
Ben, I was in the Army once.
Once is enough.
What do you mean I have to?
Arthur Hughes and General Connors
had to go all the way to the Pentagon
to get you in Chris' platoon.
And as of now, you are in the Army,
back on active duty.
Ben, how could you do this to me?
I couldn't do it to her.
Chris said he was with a girl
named Nancy Lamont
when he went AWOL. Find her.
Consider it done.
Good luck, Tyler.
Tyler,
everybody on that post treats me
like I've got the plague.
Either that or I'm a member
of the first family.
Now, your going undercover
is the only way
we're gonna be able
to investigate this thing.
But as a private, Ben?
I was an officer.
Do you realise
what you're asking of me?
How soon can you be packed?
One, two, three, four.
Left, left, left, right, left.
Wake up that guy, will you?
One, two, three, four, left, right, left.
Left, left, left, right, left...
Oh, boy, oh, boy, oh, boy.
Yo, where is everybody?
Firing range. You the new man?
- Looks that way.
- Your name?
- Hudson, Tyler.
- Rank.
- Private.
- Private?
I thought you were a general
the way you're lounging around here.
I'm Sergeant Wilson.
You get your butt into fatigues.
I'm gonna make you
my special project, private.
Morning.
Hey, you didn't tell me
you were that lawyer Ben Matlock.
- Yeah.
- My name is Danny Miller.
What can I get for you?
- A root beer?
- Yeah.
Danny,
you know, my grandfather
was a bartender
in the days of buffalo and Indians.
At a trading post, actually.
They didn't have newspapers,
but my grandfather knew everything.
Anybody wanted to know anything,
they'd ask my grandfather.
Some things never change.
- You can quote me on that.
- Maybe I will.
What do you know about
the poker game in the back room?
I'll tell you what I don't know:
why five men who
couldn't stand each other's guts
insisted on playing poker so often.
Could you just be more specific?
Here you go.
It's diet.
Not that you need it,
but it's all I've got.
Oh, thanks.
So, what can I do for you?
Well, Chris says he was here the night
Lieutenant Walters was murdered.
What time did he arrive?
Sometime after midnight.
I had just gotten off work at the bar.
And how was he when he got here?
Was he nervous or upset?
Chris didn't kill Lieutenant Walters.
He couldn't do something like that.
He tried to attack Lieutenant Walters
with a bayonet.
Did you know that?
No, I didn't, but I can tell you this:
Lieutenant Walters was a creep.
Walters used to hang out
at your bar?
Only on Saturday nights.
He'd meet these two guys
and leave right away.
What guys?
Two civilians.
Looked like a couple of hoods.
And it was the same two guys
every Saturday night?
Yeah.
Maybe that means something.
Not easy to get along with.
Well, there he is now.
That's Colonel McRea.
Just remember, Mr. Matlock,
you heard it anyplace but here.
Danny, take a lock.
Colonel McRea? Benjamin Matlock.
Glad you could make it
on such short notice.
I never turn down a free lunch.
Gentlemen?
Yeah.
I wanted to ask you
about the poker games you used
to play with Lieutenant Walters.
Just an innocent little game
of five-card draw,
jacks or better, $5 ante.
Did you win?
Sometimes.
Did you like playing
with Lieutenant Walters?
Sure.
Even though he made
a practise of insulting you?
Walters kidded me sometimes.
That's all.
Was he kidding
when he said things like
you're old, over the hill,
couldn't cut it anymore,
couldn't walk and chew gum
at the same time,
had this empty space
between your ears?
What are you driving at?
I just wonder why you'd let
a junior officer treat you that way.
He had a big mouth.
But he was okay underneath.
Where did you go
after the poker game
the night Lieutenant Walters
was killed?
Back to the supply depot.
I had some work to finish up.
Anybody else there?
After I relieved Sergeant Owens, no.
Is that the same Sergeant Owens
who said he saw Private Hughes
come out of the officers' club?
He's my duty sergeant.
You know,
that's an interesting coincidence.
If Sergeant Owens hadn't happened
to be passing by the club that night,
there'd be no way to tie Chris Hughes
to the scene of the murder.
Are you gentlemen
ready to order yet?
I've already eaten,
but I wanna take care of the colonel.
Enjoy your free lunch.
- Afternoon, sir.
Good afternoon, sir.
Oh, I apologise.
You mind if I look around?
- You see two stars on my shoulder?
- No.
Well, you gotta outrank a brigadier
general to say no to you around here,
so why don't you just be my guest?
Thanks.
Which one of these
is Chris Hughes' bunk?
These footlockers always unlocked?
That's right.
- Mind if I...?
- Go ahead.
I knew I'd find you
around here someplace.
Don't talk to me.
We can bust this case
against Chris Hughes wide open
if we can only find out
where this Sergeant Owens really was
at the time of the murder.
I am not listening.
He works at the supply depot
run by Colonel McRea.
Talk to his coworkers.
Maybe one of them knows
where he was that night.
Ben, do you see
what I'm doing here?
Now, when am I supposed
to do this talking?
I ask you, when?
Tyler,
I know how unpleasant this is,
and I can't tell you how much
I appreciate what you're doing.
And somehow I'll make it up to you.
I don't know how yet, but I will.
I swear.
What are you looking at?
You're going to be mad.
Try me.
Well,
you missed a spot.
I told you. I knew you'd be mad.
- Here you go.
- Terrific.
- You look great in my clothes.
- Thanks.
A little snug.
You'd have stuck out like a sore thumb
if you'd worn that dress in here.
I know.
So...
See that guy at the bar?
His name is Jim Lynch.
He's a lieutenant,
comes in here a lot.
Every time those two guys
I told you about showed up,
he'd leave with them
just like Lieutenant Walters did.
He's one of the men
Walters played poker with.
Looks kind of Ionely to me.
Is this seat taken?
No, it's all yours.
Thank you.
Have some pretzels.
Oh, actually, I'd like one of those.
Lee? Look, could we have
a beer for the lady, please?
You're a regular.
I come in here once in a while.
Often enough to know a new face
when I see one.
Oh, I'm just visiting
an old friend from school.
- Are you?
- Thanks.
What's your excuse?
The Army.
Oh, the Army.
Seen the world?
Just Fort Simpson
and Grenada.
You've seen actual combat.
Yes. Yes, I have
actually seen combat.
- Being all you can be?
- Yeah.
Yes.
Look, I'm very sorry.
You'll have to excuse me.
I have to go now,
but I'll see you around.
That's them.
They were gone about half an hour
and then Jim Lynch came back alone.
What did you do?
I spent another hour
talking with him.
I told him I was in town visiting
a girlfriend who works at the bar,
not Nancy.
These two fellas
that left with Jim Lynch,
what do you know about them?
Well, they're not big socialisers,
but they sure are big spenders.
Good, good.
You did good.
- You better go home now.
- No, you go home. I'm staying.
No, you better go home. We don't know
what we're getting into here, Charlene.
Well, don't you think
we'd better find out?
Dad, I might be able to get
something more out of this lieutenant.
Maybe if I talk with him
he'll let something slip.
Nancy will put me up.
Besides, her clothes even fit.
That Article 32 investigation
starts tomorrow.
I want you to be rested,
confident, cooperative.
You didn't do it,
and that's the way
I want you to look.
Are you making any progress?
- Some.
- Like what?
You have to be patient.
In other words, nothing.
That's just great.
You're in a difficult position.
There are a lot of unknowns,
but you have to know
that I have been here before,
many times.
I am doing my best
and I will do my very best.
You have to trust me on that.
- Company?
- Platoon.
Fall out.
Captain?
Captain Campbell?
May I have a word with you?
My wife is gonna pick me up
just about now.
This will only take a moment.
I just wanted to ask you some questions
about the formal complaints
that were filed against
Lieutenant Walters
- while he was under your command.
- Such as?
Well, on one occasion, he supposedly
slapped a soldier across the face,
and on another, he made a man
stand at attention in the sun
for five hours till he passed out.
Those complaints were thoroughly
investigated, Mr. Matlock.
Why was there no investigation
into Bobby Thomas' death?
There will be.
It seems to me as Lieutenant Walters'
commanding officer,
you should have been questioning him
instead of playing poker with him.
As a matter of fact, I think nothing
came of those complaints
because somebody
was looking out for him,
- kind of keeping him out of trouble.
- You mean me?
- Sooner or later, the complaints had--
- I resent what you are insinuating.
You're right.
You're right,
it doesn't make any sense.
Why cover up for Lieutenant Walters
when everybody knows
he and your wife were good friends?
What are you talking about?
Oh, I'm sorry. I thought you knew.
It's all over the post.
Bill, I was waiting for you outside.
Hello. I'm Ben Matlock.
I was just leaving.
Bill?
Like they say, three is a crowd.
Find out anything?
Someone who is positive
that they saw Sergeant Owens,
your alleged eyewitness,
in the supply depot
and not at the officers' club
at the time of the murder.
Tyler, I knew you could do it.
What's his name?
His name is Parker.
He's a sergeant.
Works in the mess as a cook.
Now, he told somebody
who told somebody.
Now I am telling you.
Ben, please,
when can I get out of here?
How can you be sure you saw
Sergeant Owens that particular night?
Well, I was working late
and I remember that
because I almost never work late.
And I remember it was
a little bit after 1 1 ,
because that's the time I got off.
And I remember
walking past the depot
and seeing Owens
all by himself and thinking:
''What do you know? Somebody else
is worse off than me for a change.''
Sergeant Parker,
you're just what the doctor ordered.
Hearing's tomorrow, 9:00.
See you then.
Right.
- Morning, Major Orlando.
- Hello, Mr. Matlock.
That's a heavy-Iooking briefcase.
I hope it's not all evidence
against my client.
I believe in being well-prepared,
even in cases as open-and-shut
as this one.
- Well, morning, Colonel.
- Good morning, Mr. Matlock.
- Major Orlando.
- General.
Yes?
- Did you get a telegram?
- No.
Yeah, well, I did.
From the old man.
''Good luck.
I'm with you all the way.''
All the way from Germany.
Well, you knew he wouldn't be here.
I guess he figures
we got it under control.
Who are you looking for?
If who I'm looking for
comes through that door,
a lot of your problems are over.
So after Colonel McRea relieved me
at the supply depot,
I headed back to my car
to drive home.
And as I passed the officers' club,
I heard this door slam.
That's when I saw Private Hughes
come out of the building and run away.
What time was that?
23:00 hours, sir.
Which, as we've already heard,
is approximately the time
that Lieutenant Walters was killed.
Thank you, Sergeant Owens.
Mr. Matlock, do you wish
to question the witness?
Yes, sir. Before I do,
I'd like to clear up a matter
concerning a witness
I had planned to call.
I'd like to request a short recess.
Very well. This hearing will reconvene
at 1 0:00 hours.
Hang on.
Sergeant Parker,
why aren't you at the hearing?
I changed my mind.
What the hell do you mean
you changed your mind?
Didn't feel like sticking my neck out
for some boy I didn't even know.
Nobody's asking you
to stick your neck out.
I want you to tell the truth.
Yeah, well, the truth is
if Owens is lying, who's he lying for?
The brass.
It's your duty to tell the truth.
You're forgetting the first rule
of this man's army:
Don't volunteer.
I can subpoena you if I have to.
Yeah, well,
why don't you just do that?
But just remember one thing:
My memory gets real bad real fast.
You know, after this court-martial,
you get to pack up
and go home, but me?
I'm a 20-year man. I get to stay here,
and with the officers, so no, thanks.
They're gonna get away
with actual murder,
and they're gonna ruin
an innocent boy's life.
Maybe you don't know
Chris Hughes,
but the next time--
And if you don't testify,
there will be a next time.
--do you know who that poor boy
might just turn out to be?
You.
Now, come on, sergeant.
What do you say?
Be just a minute.
Well, Mr. Matlock,
are you ready to proceed?
Yes, sir.
As soon as my client gets here.
That could be a long time.
Excuse me, sir.
We've searched the post
and found no sign of Private Hughes
or his belongings.
He's AWOL, possibly a deserter.
I've taken steps to have
a warrant issued for his arrest.
www.tvsubtitles.net